downloadatoz.com 2003-12-03

# Freeware Shareware Download

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

DOWNLOADATOZ.COM IS THE SOLE OWNER OF THE INFORMATION COLLECTED ON THIS SITE. WE WILL NOT SELL, SHARE, OR RENT THIS INFORMATION TO OTHERS IN WAYS DIFFERENT FROM WHAT IS DISCLOSED IN THIS STATEMENT. DOWNLOADATOZ.COM COLLECTS INFORMATION FROM OUR USERS AT SEVERAL DIFFERENT POINTS ON OUR WEBSITE.

**REGISTRATION**

ALL PROGRAMS ON THIS WEBSITE ARE FREE TO DOWNLOAD UNLESS UNLESS STATED CONTRARILY, IN ORDER TO USE THESE PROGRAMS AFTER A TRIAL PERIOD OR ACCESS TO FULL FEATURES OF THEM, A USER MAY FIRST PAY AN AMOUNT OF MONEY TO REGISTER THEM. USUALLY A USER MAY BE PROVIDED WITH AN OPTON WHETHER TO HAVE A PHYSICAL DISC OR TO DOWNLOAD AN ELECTRIC COPY. THE SHIPPING FEE OF PHYSICAL DISCS IS NOT REFUNDABLE IN ANY CHANCES.

**COOKIES**

A COOKIE IS A PIECE OF DATA STORED ON THE USER'S HARD DRIVE CONTAINING INFORMATION ABOUT THE USER. USAGE OF A COOKIE IS IN NO WAY LINKED TO ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION WHILE ON OUR SITE. ONCE THE USER CLOSES THEIR BROWSER, THE COOKIE SIMPLY TERMINATES. FOR INSTANCE, BY SETTING A COOKIE ON OUR SITE, THE USER WOULD NOT HAVE TO LOG IN A PASSWORD MORE THAN ONCE, THEREBY SAVING TIME WHILE ON OUR SITE. IF A USER REJECTS THE COOKIE, THEY MAY STILL USE OUR SITE. THE ONLY DRAWBACK TO THIS IS THAT THE USER WILL BE LIMITED IN SOME AREAS OF OUR SITE. FOR EXAMPLE, THE USER WILL NOT BE ABLE TO USE CERTAIN FEATURES OF OUR BULLETIN BOARD OR OTHER PARTS OF THE SITE THAT OFFER CUSTOMIZED SETTINGS. COOKIES CAN ALSO ENABLE US TO TRACK AND TARGET THE INTERESTS OF OUR USERS TO ENHANCE THE EXPERIENCE ON OUR SITE.

**SHARING**

WE WILL SHARE AGGREGATED DEMOGRAPHIC INFORMATION WITH OUR PARTNERS AND ADVERTISERS. THIS IS NOT LINKED TO ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT CAN IDENTIFY ANY INDIVIDUAL PERSON.

WE USE AN OUTSIDE CREDIT CARD PROCESSING COMPANY TO BILL USERS FOR GOODS AND SERVICES. THESE COMPANIES DO NOT RETAIN, SHARE, STORE OR USE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION FOR ANY SECONDARY PURPOSES. YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IS HIGHLY PROTECTED BY OUR E-COMMERCE PROVIDERS.

**LINKS**

THIS WEB SITE CONTAINS LINKS TO OTHER SITES. PLEASE BE AWARE THAT WE DOWNLOADATOZ.COM ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OF SUCH OTHER SITES. WE ENCOURAGE OUR USERS TO BE AWARE WHEN THEY LEAVE OUR SITE AND TO READ THE PRIVACY STATEMENTS OF EACH AND EVERY WEB SITE THAT COLLECTS PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION. THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT APPLIES SOLELY TO INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THIS WEB SITE.

**NEWSLETTER**

IF A USER WISHES TO SUBSCRIBE TO OUR NEWSLETTER, WE ASK FOR CONTACT INFORMATION SUCH AS NAME AND EMAIL ADDRESS.

**TELL-A-FRIEND**

IF A USER ELECTS TO USE OUR REFERRAL SERVICE FOR INFORMING A FRIEND ABOUT OUR SITE, WE ASK THEM FOR THE FRIEND'S NAME AND EMAIL ADDRESS. DOWNLOADATOZ.COM WILL AUTOMATICALLY SEND THE FRIEND A ONE-TIME EMAIL INVITING THEM TO VISIT THE SITE. DOWNLOADATOZ.COM DOESN'T STORE THIS INFORMATION AFTER SENDING AN INVITATION EMAIL.

**SECURITY**

THIS WEBSITE TAKES EVERY PRECAUTION TO PROTECT OUR USERS' INFORMATION. WHEN USERS SUBMIT SENSITIVE INFORMATION VIA THE WEBSITE, YOUR INFORMATION IS PROTECTED BOTH ONLINE AND OFF-LINE.

WHEN OUR REGISTRATION/ORDER FORM ASKS USERS TO ENTER SENSITIVE INFORMATION (SUCH AS CREDIT CARD NUMBER AND/OR SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER), THAT INFORMATION IS ENCRYPTED AND IS PROTECTED WITH THE BEST ENCRYPTION SOFTWARE IN THE INDUSTRY - SSL. WHILE ON A SECURE PAGE, SUCH AS OUR ORDER FORM, THE LOCK ICON ON THE BOTTOM OF WEB BROWSERS SUCH AS NETSCAPE NAVIGATOR AND MICROSOFT INTERNET EXPLORER BECOMES LOCKED, AS OPPOSED TO UN-LOCKED, OR OPEN, WHEN YOU ARE JUST 'SURFING'. TO LEARN MORE ABOUT SSL, FOLLOW THIS LINK HTTP://WWW.SSL.COM

**NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**

IF WE DECIDE TO CHANGE OUR PRIVACY POLICY, WE WILL POST THOSE CHANGES ON OUR HOMEPAGE SO OUR USERS ARE ALWAYS AWARE OF WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT, HOW WE USE IT, AND UNDER CIRCUMSTANCES, IF ANY, WE DISCLOSE IT. IF AT ANY POINT WE DECIDE TO USE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION IN A MANNER DIFFERENT FROM THAT STATED AT THE TIME IT WAS COLLECTED, WE WILL NOTIFY USERS BY WAY OF AN EMAIL. USERS WILL HAVE A CHOICE AS TO WHETHER OR NOT WE USE THEIR INFORMATION IN THIS DIFFERENT MANNER. WE WILL USE INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE PRIVACY POLICY UNDER WHICH THE INFORMATION WAS COLLECTED.
